Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
If God be for us who can be against us?
I'm Favour Yaje. I'm from Cameroon.
I want to share this testimony.
It is a privilege for me to stand before the people of God and viewers all over the world
to share what the Lord has done for me through Emmanuel TV.
Indeed, distance is not a barrier.
This is what the Lord has done for me through Emmanuel TV.
I was delivered from the spirit of masturbation and bed-wetting which I had for more than 20 years.
These two problems I mentioned almost took away my life.
I want to thank the Lord for the medium of Emmanuel TV.
Hallelujah!
Can you explain to us how these problems started in your life?
This all started when...
I was bed-wetting since when I was growing up.
At certain age, the thing was like... I cannot explain because it was happening...
There was a certain period whereby once in every month, I would bed-wet, no matter what happened.
I would have a particular nightmare and when I would wake up, I would notice that I had bed-wet.
This problem came; I was not like other people.
I could not explain it.
It was something that I didn’t know how to explain.
There was a particular period of time it would happen;
there was a particular period of time every month that it used to occur.
I had tried everything.
When that period of time would come, I would try not to sleep.
I would keep myself awake but when I laid down, even at 5am it would happen.
This really was a disgrace to me.
There was nothing I could do about it.
Can you explain to us how this problem affected your relationship with your friends and your family members?
With my friends and family members, those who were close to me,
right now, I know that many of them will be surprised;
nobody knew that this was the problem that I was having.
Because at times, all I know that
there was a particular period of time I wouldn’t go out with my friends
and I wouldn’t sleep elsewhere because I knew that I would bet-wet.
That had kept me away from my friends; except I really trusted someone, I would tell them
that this was the problem that I was having.
They would ask what my problem was called and why I would only bed-wet during a particular period
but I could not explain.
You also mentioned that you had the problem of masturbation.
Can you explain to us how this problem started and how it affected your life?
The problem of masturbation was a very big problem because I had this problem for three years.
The problem started in 2008.
I was lying down and I heard a voice telling me to masturbate.
I tried to resist but there was no way.
I tried to keep myself but there was no way.
Until...
I then masturbated; I said, “if it is only once, I will do it”.
I thought that if I did it once, God would forgive me.
But when I did it once, that was how I became addicted.
I could not resist; I would hear that voice.
If I was standing in front of the mirror, it was as if I was seeing a different person.
The thought would keep coming to me; I could not resist.
Even if I wanted to pray, I wouldn’t be able to until I did it.
This is the problem that had really tormented me because each time I would masturbate,
when it was over I would be regretting, “Why did I do this thing?”
But there was no way I could stop doing it.
I fasted and prayed but after the prayer, it would still happen.
There was nothing I could do about it.
Can you tell us how you were finally delivered from these problems? How did it take place?
I was delivered through Emmanuel TV.
There was a day I got angry at myself; I said, “This cannot continue”.
I touched the screen (of Emmanuel TV) by faith.
Then, as I touched the screen while the man of God was praying,
my body started shivering; I couldn’t control myself.
But I don’t know what happened later.
It is later that I noticed that the month had come and gone.
I was thinking that I was going to bet-wet but that period of time came and passed.
There is something very important I want to share with you and the viewers.
When that period of time came, I had that nightmare I used to have -
I would urinate in the dream and when I woke up, I would find the bed wet.
But when I woke up, I was so surprised.
Hallelujah!
I was surprised to find that when I woke up, there was not even a drop and I didn't feel like urinating.
This is a sign that God had already done it but I still didn't believe.
It was after one year, when I noticed that I do not bed-wet anymore.
Let's put our hand together for Jesus Christ!
You mean that after praying with the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua through Emmanuel TV
by putting your hand on the screen of Emmanuel TV you realised that the problem of bed-wetting
has completely stopped?
Yes, I realised the problem stopped.
It is almost two years that the problem has stopped.
Hallelujah!
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for the miracle worker - Jesus Christ!
Our sister explained to us earlier this was a problem that you grew up with.
Since she could remember from her childhood, she had been bed-wetting and for 20 years
she suffered from this problem.
But the moment she put her hand on the screen, prayed with the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua
through Emmanuel TV she was delivered effectually and completely from the problem of bed-wetting.
This has now been for how many years?
It had been 20 years.
For how long have you now been delivered?
I have been delivered for two years.
Hallelujah! In fact a million thanks are not enough for Jesus Christ.
Can you also explain to us how have you been delivered from the problem of masturbation?
I was delivered from the problem of masturbation through Emmanuel TV
and praying along with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
When I prayed, the problem was over but I didn’t know that it was over.
When I realised, it was more than one month later.
When I would stand in front of the mirror, it was as though I was seeing a different person.
I noticed that since then, when I stand in front of the mirror, that thought no longer comes to me.
When I would think of what I used to do in the past, it irritated me.
I had started watching pornographic movies.
Since I was delivered, I hate it.
I no longer enjoy seeing women or men naked.
This is the sign that God has done it for me.
These miracles, this deliverance took place in the same time period
because I came in contact with Emmanuel TV last year.
Hallelujah.
Indeed we can see that Jesus Christ has set you free.
He has put an end to your past and given birth to the future that you have been longing for such a long time.
Can you tell us what advice do you have for people out there?
We know that there are millions people out there watching now and they are also suffering
of a similar problem.
What advice do you have for them?
I advise people that the shame belongs to the devil, not to you.
Hallelujah.
Any problem that you are going through, there are many young girls like me, going through this problem
of masturbation, that shame – that you don’t want people to know what you are doing -
the shame belongs to the devil.
I want to advise people to watch Emmanuel TV.
You may not have the Anointing Sticker or the Anointing Water or any of those mediums
but through watching Emmanuel TV, God is going to transform your life.
God has done it for me.
Develop the habit of watching Emmanuel TV and praying along with the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The special day came where I received my miracle; you own day is coming.
Submit your problems to the Lord.
Hallelujah.
[Amen]
Indeed we can see that our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ has put an end to the past life of shame in our sister's
life, and He's given a bright future.
Her past is indeed over.
Sister, now that you have been delivered from this problem we want to encourage you
to continue to follow Jesus on the way, make God's Word a standard for your life, so you can maintain
this deliverance, in Jesus' name.
Addicted To Masturbation; Afflicted To Bedwet | Emmanuel TV Testimony
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today,
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons, and testimonies from SCOAN
Emmanuel TV; changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.
TT ROBERT BEGIER 22/06/2018